Finding Aid for the RecorDIM Project Records of the Getty Conservation Institute Field Projects Division, 1994-2009, undated IA10016
Institutional Records and Archives
- Visuals
  - RecorDIM_06 Meetings images .jpg images, website images, 2005-2007